(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
【開演までしばらくお待ちください】
[Opening Card: Please wait a moment until the concert begins]
【ATTENTION / ご来場のお客様へ】演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
[Attention: To all attendees / Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start soon. Please wait.
照明の明滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment.
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
アニメにハマって
I got hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった！
and now I really want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて
Being able to sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてつらい！
...is so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND!
holoplus Jack 本日22時まで！
holoplus Jack: Until 22:00 today!
本日は...
Today...
秘密結社holoX ファーストライブ 2026 ファーストミッションにご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Secret Society holoX First Live 2026: First MISSION!
自己紹介！心服せよ！
Self-introduction! Obey me!
吾輩の名前はラプラス・ダークネスだ！
My name is La+ Darknesss!
皆さん、待った？
Did I keep you waiting, everyone?
待った！
We waited!
holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します。
I am the executive of holoX, Takane Lui.
みんな、こんこよ！
Everyone, Konkoyo!
こんこよ！
Konkoyo!
holoXの頭脳、博衣コヨリだよ！
I'm holoX's brain, Hakui Koyori!
ござるさんはー？
Who is Gozaru-san?
風真！
Kazama!
お〜、よくできたでござる！holoXの用心棒、一期一会を大切に、風真いろはでござる！
Oh, well done! holoX's bodyguard, valuing once-in-a-lifetime encounters, Kazama Iroha here!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show to the very end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機器の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, or the use of recording equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you feel unwell, do not push yourself and please inform a nearby staff member.
良い子です。
Good boys and girls.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他の皆さんの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, throwing objects onto the stage, or any other acts that cause trouble for others or obstruct the performance are strictly prohibited inside the venue.
また、3階と4階の最前列席は、危険防止のため、立ち見禁止です。
Also, standing to watch from the front rows of the 3rd and 4th floors is prohibited for safety reasons.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time.
お守りいただけない場合、ご退場いただく可能性がございます。
If you do not follow them, you may be asked to leave.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Additionally, video streaming and photography cameras are inside the venue today, and the audience seats may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
いい返事でござるな！
What a good response!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、『#SSホロックス世界再ペイント計画』です！
Also, the hashtag for the live show is #SSholoXWorldRepaintProject!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Use the hashtag to get everyone super hyped!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Now, there are only a few moments left until the show starts!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるでござる！
Let's all get hyped up together!
みんな、しーっ。
Everyone, shh.
静かに、しーっ...
Be quiet, shh...
もうきみの心 チクっとしちゃえ
Let me give your heart a little prick!
わおーん！
Waoon!
絶対無理思っちゃうし
I always end up thinking "absolutely impossible!"
だってだって不安になるし
Because, because, I get so anxious!
全然嘘つけないし
And I can't lie at all,
だってだってバカ真っ直ぐだし
Because, because, I'm foolishly straightforward!
目指すキラキラもきっとぼく次第だ
The sparkling light I aim for is surely up to me,
ビター？
Bitter?
ギブアップなんて言わないんだから
Because I'll never say I give up!
じっとしてらんないし
I can't just stand still,
だってだって動いちゃう脚
Because, because, my feet keep moving!
1, 1, ステップアップ
One, one, step up,
ちょっとずつ進めば夢の式解けちゃうの
If I go bit by bit, the formula of dreams will be solved!
なりたいぼくを
The me I want to be,
きみが好きなぼくを
The me that you love,
ちゃんと余りなく魅せたいの
I want to show you all of it without leaving anything behind!
あっちゃっちゃ
Ah-cha-cha!
びっくりするほどできないじゃん
I'm surprisingly unable to do it,
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
Always making mistakes and worrying,
けどきみに見つけてほしくて
But I want you to find me,
ぼくはきみを迎えに行くんだ 出会えたならハッピー
So I'll go to meet you, if we meet, it'll be happy!
わーお わーおだ 叫んじゃえ
Wao, wao, let's shout it out!
泣いて 鳴いて 愛して 尻尾振って
Crying, howling, loving, and wagging my tail,
わーお わーおだ 叫んじゃえ
Wao, wao, let's shout it out!
だめなぼくをどうか覚えておいて
Please remember the useless me,
もうきみの心 チクっとしちゃえ
Let me give your heart a little prick!
もうどうしようとかたまに思っちゃって沈んだり
Sometimes I wonder what to do and sink down,
案外いけるかも ふわり浮かんじゃって元通り
But maybe it'll unexpectedly work out, floating back to normal,
ベッタ リがやめられない
I can't stop being clingy,
おすわりってそれ何だっけ？
Wait, what does 'sit' mean again?
うっかりがとめられない
I can't stop being careless,
また歩いて棒に当たるの
Walking and hitting a pole again!
1, 1, ステップアップ
One, one, step up,
死んだふりしてるのやめて はいこっちおいで
Stop pretending to be dead, come over here!
欲しがるきみと あげすぎなぼくとで
With you always wanting, and me giving too much,
もっといける気がしています
I feel like we can go even further!
あっちゃっちゃ
Ah-cha-cha!
びっくりするほどできないじゃん
I'm surprisingly unable to do it,
間違って悩んだりばっかりじゃん
Always making mistakes and worrying,
けどきみに見つけてほしくて
But I want you to find me,
ぼくはきみを迎えに行くんだ 出会えたならハッピー
So I'll go to meet you, if we meet, it'll be happy!
だって
Because,
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社…
We who rule the star of Eden, the Secret Society...
holoX!!
かかれー！
Charge!
機は熟した！
The time is ripe!
暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ
Spirits who appear from the dawn darkness...
準備はいいか！！
Are you ready?!
行くぞー！！
Let's go!!
are you ready?
ラッパッパー lapa lapa ラッパッパー
Rappappa lapa lapa rappappa
lapata lapata ラッパッパー
Lapata lapata rappappa!
ラッパッパー lapa lapa ラッパッパー
Rappappa lapa lapa rappappa
lapata lapata ラッパッパー
Lapata lapata rappappa!
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
The night deepens, look, Darkness
能ある鷹はponで隠す
A capable hawk hides it with "pon"
脳に従え エゴイスティック
Obey the brain, egoistic
のっと！ ニンニン!! サムライgirl...
Nott! Nin-nin!! Samurai girl
闇金しないけど
I don't do loan sharking, but
フルベットでしょ
It's a full bet, right?
シャンシャン！シャンシャン！
Shanshan! Shanshan!
征服すればおk
If we conquer, it's OK
切り裂く赤字
Cut through the deficit,
ジャキン！ジャキン！
Jakin! Jakin!
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
You want to dance on the palm of evil
ほら君も 気付けば ノリノリです
Look, you're also rocking along before you know it
どうしようもない don't show, no mine
It can't be helped, don't show, no mine
堕ちてく運命 ならしょうがない...
If it's the fate of falling, it can't be helped
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything
xとxとxとxが交差する 真ん中で
In the center where x, x, x, and x intersect
next next next 世界はもう始まってるじゃん!!!!
Next, next, next, the world has already begun!!!!
(ウォッオッオ オー オー オー)
Woah oh oh oh oh oh!
飛びな to be now
Jump, to be now!
闇が呼ぶ方へ
Towards where the darkness calls
(ウォッオッオ オー オー オー)
Woah oh oh oh oh oh!
暗黒の...
Darkness of...
エクスです！
Exdesu!
混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！皆の者、かかれ！
We will repaint this chaotic world in holoX colors! Everyone, attack!
yes my dark!!!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
魔眼ホークアイ！
Demon eye Hawk Eye!
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The star of Eden is in my hands!
ラッパッパー lapa lapa ラッパッパー
Rappappa lapa lapa rappappa
lapata lapata ラッパッパー
Lapata lapata rappappa!
ラッパッパー lapa lapa ラッパッパー
Rappappa lapa lapa rappappa
lapata lapata ラッパッパー
Lapata lapata rappappa!
風穴 開けたんだ
I've opened a wind hole
支配は 始まった
The domination has begun
息はもう かけたの バズワードの
Have you already placed your breath? Of buzzwords
自覚ない はずよ
You shouldn't be aware
抑えきれない 磁力 制御不能のパワー
Unstoppable magnetism, uncontrollable power
捕まえてみなよ 影も形もない my heart
Try to catch my heart, which has no shadow or form
半信半疑の そぶりは なしの
With no sign of half-belief and half-doubt
心に 従って
Obey your heart
証明して みせてよ 今こそ
Show and prove it, right now
レミドレミド
Re-Mi-Do-Re-Mi-Do
ラッパッパー lapa lapa ラッパッパー
Rappappa lapa lapa rappappa
絡み日々ミックスになるでしょう
Entangled days will become a mix, right?
ラッパッパー lapa lapa ラッパッパー
Rappappa lapa lapa rappappa
並ぶ日々満ち足りてないなら
If the lined up days are not satisfying
イエス ダブルタップで エンジェルでしょう
Yes, with a double tap, you're an angel, right?
革命的存在を
A revolutionary existence
イエス ダブルタップで 大誕生
Yes, with a double tap, a grand birth!
吹き去って
Blow away!
...ラッパッパッパラ
...La pa pa pa pa...
どうしようもない この世界
This helpless world...
(どうして欲しい？)
(What do you want me to do?)
black out
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell tolling the end is ringing.
ラッパッパッパラ
Rappa ppappa ra,
パって踊ろうぜ trip しようぜ
let's dance and take a trip.
陰キャも陽キャも sing a song
Introverts and extroverts alike, sing a song!
気持ちいいことだけがすべて
Pleasant things are all that matter.
堕ちていく闇の底へ
Falling to the bottom of the darkness.
甘い甘いメロディ
A sweet, sweet melody.
ほらどうぞどうぞ手の鳴る方へ
Come, step right up, follow the clapping hands.
まつろわぬ我がホロックス
Our unyielding holoX,
お前もホロックスの一員となるのだ！
you too shall become a member of holoX!
So warning...
To be unclean...
Do you remember me?
注文は？と面倒くさがったあの時とは違った
Unlike back then when I sounded annoyed asking "What's your order?"
マインドも丸くなったかな
I wonder if my attitude has softened a bit.
それとも winking winking 逃げてもずっとわかってた
Or is it winking, winking... I knew it all along even if I ran.
I'm playing in the typhoon's eye, wink
ちょっとお眼鏡に適いたい
I want to catch your eye a little,
目に入れても痛くないくらい
enough that it wouldn't hurt even if I were in your eye.
らららら口馬鹿に
La-la-la-la, playfully mocking,
sweet vengeance
憎しみはとっくに捨てた
I threw away hatred a long time ago.
怖がってんの？
Are you scared?
ふーん、あっそ
Hmph, is that so?
お望み通りだ
Just as you wished.
まだまだ
Not yet, not yet.
安全じゃないから
Because it's not safe,
健全じゃないから
Because it's not wholesome,
それが何だっていうんだ
So what of it?
Blink, blink
eye to eye
目には目を
An eye for an eye,
Wink
知らないわ 好きならラッキー
I don't know, if you like me, you're lucky.
Give me a wink
知らないわ 嫌いならお気の毒
I don't know, if you hate me, what a pity.
Oh eye eye eye want you で倍々倍ヤ
Oh, eye eye, I want you, multiplying by double, double, double,
目に物見せる my heart
I'll show them what I've got, my heart.
いいよ
Fine,
目を瞑る半分ね
I'll close one eye, just halfway,
魔眼 wink
Evil eye wink.
Wink
お気の毒
What a pity.
Give me a wink
知らないわ 嫌いならお気の毒
I don't know, if you hate me, what a pity.
ホログラム 瞬く間に
In the blink of a hologram,
I kill you...
Wink
I want you
知らないわ 嫌いならお気の毒
I don't know, if you hate me, what a pity.
キャリブレーション！
Calibration!
これで決まります！
This will decide it!
こよりに メロメロ～！
Head over heels for Koyori~!
はい、みんなの脳みそに
Yes, into everyone's brains,
お注射しちゃうぞ！
I'm going to give you an injection!
実験だ！実験だ！実験 実験 実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment, it's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
一緒に！
Together!
いっくよー！
Here we go!
実験だ！実験だ！実験 実験 実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！実験だー！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment, it's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, Thank you, thank you, 処方中
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, currently prescribing.
弱った精神に劇薬パピプペポン！
To a weakened spirit, a powerful medicine - pa-pi-pu-pe-pon!
健康！健康！健康！テンションアップテンションプリーズ！
Healthy! Healthy! Healthy! Tension up, tension please!
ダメって言われたらやりたくなっちゃうよ！
When told "no", it just makes me want to do it!
迷ったら ダメダメ 迷わずにたくさん Yes!
If you hesitate, no, no! Without hesitation, a big "Yes"!
迷える子羊は迷わずこっちっち！
Lost sheep, head this way without hesitation!
こよりのデータで こよりはハッピー
With Koyori's data, Koyori is happy!
こよりについてこい！でしょ？でしょ？
Follow Koyori! Right? Right?
1, 2, 3 サンプル収集完了 臨時被験者
1, 2, 3 sample collection complete, temporary test subjects!
特殊な体質に感謝感激！
Deeply grateful for your unique constitution!
天才 天才 天才 とんでもなく有能
Genius, genius, genius! Unbelievably talented!
お邪魔しちゃって OK? 本名伏せてサインして！
Is it OK if I intrude? Sign here with a fake name!
最高 最高 最高 飛んでいって優秀
The best, the best, the best! Flying high and excellent!
うっちゃらの内緒内緒 サービスオープン！
My personal secret, secret... Service open!
1, 2, 3... 4, 5, 6...
星降るピポパ 間違い探しのドクター
Starry pipopa, the spot-the-difference doctor,
あっちなとこも 計算通り！
even those parts are just as calculated!
実験だ！実験だ！実験 実験 実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment, it's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
実験だ！実験だ！実験 実験 実験だ！ 実験だ！実験だ！実験だー！
It's an experiment! It's an experiment! Experiment, experiment, it's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment! It's an experiment!
さあさあもっと声出せるよね！
Come on, come on, you can make more noise, right?!
じゃあ一緒に『実験だ』って叫ぶよ！
Then together, let's shout, "It's an experiment"!
せーの、実験だーー！
Ready, set, IT'S AN EXPERIMENT!
もういっちょ実験だいくよー！
Let's do "It's an experiment" one more time!
せーの、実験だーーー！
Ready, set, IT'S AN EXPERIMENT!
ありがとうーー！
Thank you!
いざ、推して参る！
Now, I step forward!
一刀両断 叩き斬る！
I'll cut you in two!
煌々と夜更け ほのか歌う
Faintly singing as the night glows brightly.
花の根になりたい
I want to become the root of a flower.
ひとつ その前より しかと地に立ちたい
First, I want to stand more firmly on the ground than before.
唇を芽吹かせる
Making my lips bud.
八百万 of the rain of eight million gods falls,
Even if the rain of eight million gods falls,
ただ一時の怯むことなく
Without flinching even for a single moment,
八百万の声をとどろかせ
Letting the voices of eight million resound,
故にありし日の記憶にできるから
Because we can make it a memory of the days gone by.
涙ぐむのも 満ちるのも手向け
Tears and fulfillment are both an offering,
深く咲く
Blooming deeply.
私を認めなければ愛されないか
If you don't acknowledge me, will I not be loved?
歪なこの命に何を残してやれるだろうか
What can I leave behind for this distorted life?
叫びをあげるくらい
Enough to cry out,
身を切るくらいに凪を打つ
Striking a calm enough to cut through my body,
有り明けの先で
Beyond the dawn.
煌々と夜更け ほのか歌う
Faintly singing as the night glows brightly.
どうしようもない
It can't be helped,
It can't be helped.
交わしていく目
Our eyes meet,
目は離さない
And I won't take my eyes off you.
全部塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything.
刮目せよ！
Look closely!
エクス！ エクス！ エクス！ エクス！
X! X! X! X!
エクスが交差する真ん中で
At the center where the X crosses,
ネクスト！ ネクスト！ ネクスト！ ネクスト！
Next! Next! Next! Next!
世界はもう始まってる
The world has already begun!
さあ、ウォッオーオー
Now, woah-oh-oh!
コピーなら コンプリート なりたいストーリー
If it's a copy, complete the story I want to be.
ウォッオーオー
Woah-oh-oh!
笑うのは ホロのステージ
Laughing on the Holo stage,
ラッパッパ ラッパッパッパッパ
Lappappa lappappappappa
イェーイ！
Yeeey!
ホロックスのライブが始まったぞー！
holoX's live has started!
おにぎわー！
Onigiwa!
こんにちはー！
Hello!
こんちゃ、秘密結社でーす！
Hello, we are Secret Society!
全然ひ、ひ、秘匿性のない秘密結社！
A secret society with absolutely no secrecy!
自己紹介しよう！
Let's introduce ourselves!
はい！
Yes!
さあ！ 狂気の宴の始まりだー！
Now! The feast of madness is beginning!
貴様ら、刮目せよ！
You bastards, look closely!
我輩の名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスだー！
My name is Laplus Darkness!
イェーイ！
Yeeey!
そして...
And next...
はい！
Yes!
みなさん、まったー？
Everyone, did you wait?
新しいのよ！
That's a new one!
すごいやってくれた、みんな
Everyone really joined in!
ホロックスの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します！
I am holoX's female executive, Takane Lui!
待った？ 待った？
Did you wait? Did you wait?
イェーイ！
Yeeey!
そして...
And next...
はーい！
Yes!
え、ちょっと新しいの行きます。くる、くる、くる...
Uh, I'll try a new one. Here it comes, here it comes...
あの子より？
Than that girl?
その子より？
Than this girl?
沙花叉よりー！
Than Sakamata!
お、いけてるじゃん、すごい！
Oh, you got it! Amazing!
ありがとう！ 初めてやりました！
Thank you! That was my first time doing it!
ホロックスの掃除屋、沙花叉クロヱだよ！
I am holoX's cleaner, Sakamata Chloe!
そして...
And next...
お待たせ！ 分かってるよね？ 分かってるよね？
Thanks for waiting! You know it, right? You know it, right?
どうかな？ 濁らせてるけど、行くよ！
How about it? Let's go!
ござるさんはー？
As for Gozaru-san...?
あ、なんかちょっと内部の人間が変なこと言ってますが...
Ah, someone on the inside is saying something weird, but...
ホロックスの用心棒...
holoX's bodyguard...
つよつよカッコいい用心棒、侍の、風真いろはでござる！
The strong and cool bodyguard, samurai, Kazama Iroha is here!
うーん... はぁ...
Wow... *sigh*
ついにこの日が来てしまった。
Finally, this day has come.
始まっちゃった。み、ミスらなかった。
It has begun. I-I didn't mess up.
よかった。あぶないあぶない。
Thank goodness. That was close, that was close.
あ、最初のメドレー、凄かったでしょ！
Ah, the first medley was amazing, wasn't it?
みんなこんな風に混ざってソロ来るって予想できてたー？
Did everyone expect that we'd mix together like this for the solos?
イェーイ！/ピンクの人.../ごつっ！
Yay!/The pink person.../Thud!
だよね、だよね。予想外よね。
Right, right. It was unexpected.
もう、最初からクライマックス。
It's already a climax from the very beginning.
それぐらいの盛り上がりではある。始まったばっかだけどね。
The excitement is already at that level. Though it's just started.
始まったばっかといえばさ、みんなあの自己紹介の時に、実はみんなもうちょっとウルッときてて。
Speaking of just starting, during the self-introductions, everyone was actually already getting a bit teary-eyed.
やめてよ、その話は！
Stop it, don't talk about that!
いや、なんならもう、楽屋の時点で、ルイさんは、一番早かったのはルイさん！
Actually, even back in the dressing room, Lui-san... The earliest one to cry was Lui-san!
いやいやいや！違うの違うの！違うの！
No, no, no! That's not it, that's not it! That's not it!
花粉症！
Hay fever!
ごまかすなよ！/ごまかしてない！
Don't try to cover it up!/I'm not covering it up!
花粉症！
It's hay fever!
いいじゃん、素直になれば。メンバー大好きで泣きだし.../泣きだしてない！
Come on, just be honest. You started crying because you love the members.../I didn't start crying!
やめてよ！
Stop it!
それをみんなでいじってたのに、
We were teasing her about it, but...
ここに来てみんなの笑顔を見たらさ.../いや、そう。
But when we came out here and saw everyone's smiles.../Well, yes.
なんか、始まる前はさ、みんなこんなんで待ってたのに。
Like, before it started, everyone was waiting like this.
自己紹介が始まった瞬間、うぅーってなって、
But the moment the self-introductions started, we were like, 'Ugh...'
めちゃくちゃ笑顔でうぅーってなって、
trying to smile so hard while tearing up.
みんなの声とか音とかが凄くて、みんな泣いてた。
Everyone's voices and the sound were so amazing, everyone was crying.
そう、ウルッときて、でも「やらなきゃ！」ってやったんだよね。
Right, we got teary-eyed, but we thought, 'We have to do this!' and we did it.
やら、やらないといけないよね。
We, we have to do it.
もう、今日はかまさないといけないよ。
We really have to blow everyone away today.
でも、1曲目はかませたんじゃないか？
But didn't we blow them away with the first song?
かませてたー？
Did we blow you away?
ちょっとさ、最初の曲のメドレーのさ、タイトル言ってやってよ。
Hey, tell them the title of that first medley.
ちょっと待って、これ読むの？めっちゃかっこよく言えるよ。
Wait a minute, I have to read this? I can say it really coolly.
みんな、まぁ「GyoukouX」は知ってるよね？
Everyone, you all know 'GyoukouX', right?
今日のための特別タイトルあるから。
Because there's a special title just for today.
そうなのよ、叫ぶから。
Yes, because she's going to shout it.
いくぞ！
Here we go!
「GyoukouX...」
'GyoukouX...'
「GyoukouX-tended Remix みんなの殺意を詰め込んでみましたバージョン」！
'GyoukouX-tended Remix: We Tried Packing in Everyone's Murderous Intent Version'!
なんか最後、ちょっと...
The end was a bit...
そのままじゃない？無理やりじゃない？
Isn't that just literal? Isn't that a bit forced?
かっけえ。
So cool.
決まったぜ。
I nailed it.
配信組も盛り上がってますかー？
Are the stream viewers pumped up too?
配信組も頑張るでござるよ！
Let's do our best, stream viewers!
コメントも見えてるからね。
We can see your comments too.
コメントも「イェーイ」「うおー」しか言ってない。
The comments are just saying 'Yay' and 'Whoa'.
「タイトル長い」って言われてる。
They're saying, 'The title is too long'.
長くないよ！吾輩の名前より短いじゃん。
It's not long! It's shorter than my name, isn't it?
それはそう。
That's true.
そういえば、みんな開演前から気づいたと思うけど、
By the way, I think everyone noticed before the show started, but...
DJ！
The DJ!
最高だよ！落ちないようにね！
It's the best! Make sure you don't fall off!
本当だよ。ちょっと怖いよ絶対。超たけえし。
Really. It must be a bit scary up there. It's super high.
というわけで、ここから先は、本当の任務に入っていくぞ！
And so, from here on, we're heading into the real mission!
なんですけど、ここで...
But, at this point...
いやだ！吾輩は聞かない！
No! I won't listen!
まさか、まさか...
Don't tell me, don't tell me...
ちょっと私から言うのもあれなんで、コヨちゃんお願いします。/おいおいおい！人の口を借りるな！
It's a bit awkward for me to say it, so Koyo-chan, please./Hey, hey, hey! Don't make me say it!
はい、ではちょっと大事なお知らせです。
Alright, we have an important announcement.
YouTube、TikTokライブでご覧になっている方、無料チラ見せパートはここまでとなります！
For those watching on YouTube or TikTok Live, the free preview part ends here!
うわー！/関係ないのに「えー」って言ってくれてる。
Whoa!/Even though it doesn't affect them, they're saying 'Eee' for us.
ですが！この後も、あんなパフォーマンスや、ゴージャスな楽曲など、
But! Even after this, there will be performances like that and gorgeous songs,
今からでも間に合いますので、この辺、概要欄から、この辺、配信チケットを購入してください！
You can still make it, so please purchase a streaming ticket from around here, the description box, or around here!
ここ、ここ！/ここ、ここです！
Here, here!/Here, right here!
欲張りセット。音がした。これでいこう。
The greedy set. Sounds. Let's do this.
お前ら、絶対買えよな！買った音した、買った音。
You guys, make sure you buy it! I heard the sound of buying, the sound of buying.
はい、ここで！
Yes, and now!
じゃ、ここからね、さっき言った通り、本当のミッション始まりますよね！
Well then, from here on, just like we said earlier, the real mission is going to begin!
はい！
Yes!
おーい！まだ声出せるよなー！
Hey! You can still make some noise, right?!
最高です！
Awesome!
ここにいる全員、そして配信のみんな！覚悟はいいかー！
Everyone here, and everyone watching the stream! Are you ready?!
ファーストミッション、ここからが本番だー！
First Mission, the real show starts now!
それでは、任務続行！
Well then, mission resume!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.